(Bernadette(on screen):)And you should pick me
(Bernadette(on screen):)for Miss California Quiznos
1999, because I want to...
(rhythmically):
Tell you what I want,
what I really really want
I'll tell you what I want,
(Bernadette(on screen):)I wanna, I wanna,
I wanna, I wanna
(Bernadette(on screen):)Really, really, really be
Miss California Quiznos 1999!
Play it again!
(laughing)
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Did he respond yet?
(Sheldon:)Hmm. No, not yet.
(Leonard:)Well,
(Leonard:)maybe we shouldn't have sunk
to his level.
(Howard:)It wasn't that bad.
(Leonard:)Read it back one more time.
(clears throat)
"My good sir, we are neither
crackpots nor wannabes.
"In fact, we are
experts in our fields.
"And while you hide
behind your anonymity,
"we stand behind our paper.
And later tonight, your mother."
(Leonard:)And you don't think
that's too rough?